It's really style.
めっちゃスタイルやん
amazing.
すごい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's a bit embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい状態
Well then, no underwear.
じゃあ、下着ねーじゃんか
Oh, that's cute.
おー、可愛い
It's cute.
可愛いね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
I'm really embarrassed.
めちゃめちゃ恥ずかしいんですけど
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
I'm starting to get nervous.
ギンギンになってきちゃった
it was fun.
楽しかった
OK, let's talk then.
OK、じゃあ、しゃべよっか
Look here.
こっち見てよ
Show me this.
こ っち見せてさ
Come on, look.
さあ、見て
Maybe I should try that.
そこをやってみようかな
Wow, it's beautiful.
うわー、きれいだねー
This will cut your hair.
髪がきれるじゃん、これ
yes.
そう
My hair is getting cut off, it's embarrassing.
髪がきれるじゃん、恥ずかしい
What's good?
どこがいいの?
picture?
え?
What do you think?
どうだよ
yes?
そう?
Look, look.
ほら、見て
Wow, it's so muffled.
うわ、すげーこもっちゃう
Oh my gosh.
やべーやべー
I'm feeling a little stuffy, so I think I'll go to bed.
ちょっとこもっちゃうから、寝ようかな
Your hair is white.
髪白いねー
Were you told that there is no dye?
色素ないって言われましたっか
oh.
お ー
I want to see it behind me.
後ろに見たい
yeah?
ん?
I want to see it behind me.
後ろに見たい
Awesome.
すげー
what?
何?
You can enter with your face.
顔で入っちゃっていいよ
I put it in.
入れました
Did you put it in?
入れた?
yes.
はい
what?
何?
Are you going to do this?
こっちゃうの?
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Awesome, so cute.
すごい、かわいい
funny.
おもしろい
You're really good at it.
すごい上手だね
While looking at me.
こっち見ながらなんて
Soooo, a little, soooo, I licked it a little.
すげー、ちょっと、すげー、ちょっとペロペロした
yeah?
ん?
Perope
ペロペ
B.
ロ
yeah?
ん?
Even if I take my hands off?
手 外しても?
hand?
手?
This way
こっち
only.
だけ
Yeah.
うん
Push it with your hands.
手 だし押して
Yeah.
うん
Oh, that's terrible.
あーやばい
Get it down.
下だして
He stopped me again.
もう一回止めてくれた
Ah ah ah.
あーあーあー
Hmmmm.
んふふふ
ah.
あー
Press again.
もう一回押して
yeah?
ん?
What does it taste like?
どんな味?
I wonder what it was, hmm, it was delicious.
何だろう、んー、美味しかった
That's a lie.
嘘だ
What should I answer?
なんて答えればいいの?
Wow, that's a good kid.
すごい、いい子なんだね
We all did it.
全員やったわ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいで